How did you drop your
textbook in the water?
Ah, my bathtub study tray broke.
You have a bathtub study tray?
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Hi.
Hey.
'Yo.
Why do you have a bowling bowl?
Don't ask why.
Just pretend you don't see it and
that way, we won't be a part
of the tragedy that's about to happen.
Hey, all set.
Okay, people, unless you're
a bowling pin, move.
[Cheering]
Ha, no way you can knock
both of them down.
Don't doubt my ball skills.
What's wrong with Ms. Ackerman?
What'd you do to her, Sam?
I know why miss Ackerman is upset.
Why?
What happened?
Her boyfriend dumped her last night.
No way.
What?
Yup.
You didn't hear it from me.
[Bell ringing]
I got to get to class.
Sure.
Right after I knock down
these last two pins.
With one throw?
Not possible.
We'll see.
Ow.
I'll call the school nurse.
[Music]
♪ I know you'll see, somehow
the world will change for me
and be so wonderful, live life,
breathe air, I know somehow
we're gonna get there and feel
so wonderful, it's all for real,
I'm telling you just how I feel, so
wake up the members of my nation,
it's your time to be, there's no chance
unless you take one and the time
to see the brighter side of every
situation, some things are meant to be,
so give me your best and leave the
rest to me, leave it all to me,
leave it all to me, just
leave it all to me *
Sync by honeybunny
<font color="
This is super weird.
She's been like that for 20 minutes.
I'm gonna go talk to her.
Miss Ackerman, are you okay?
Yes.
Sit down.
Okay.
Now, I want you all to write a 10-page
essay on the Louisiana purchase.
Um, we haven't even gotten
to that chapter yet.
Too bad.
Sometimes, things happen
you're not prepared for.
But how are we suppose to
write an essay on something
you haven't taught us about yet?
I don't need your sass, carly shay.
Sass?
Look, it's not fair to make us write
10 pages-- let's make it 15 pages,
yeah, that's right.
Ow.
I'm gonna go get some aspirin.
Start reading chapter whatever.
I'm not sassy.
Her boyfriend must
have dumped her hard.
No kidding.
The lady is losing it.
Sometimes I'm bold,
but I'm never sassy.
Freddie, why aren't you
reading chapter whatever?
Oh, um, 'cause I dropped my
textbook in the bathtub last night.
Of course.
You men are all the same.
You lose interest in your textbook
and then you just dump it
in your filthy bath water.
Ms. Ackerman, you don't need
to yell at Freddie in front
of the whole class.
Oh, look, more back talk
from the sass master.
I am not the sass master.
And it's wrong for you to be mean to
Freddie just 'cause your boyfriend
broke up with you.
Wow, Carls.
Maybe you are the sass master.
You go straight to the
principal's office.
What?
You heard me.
But-- go.
Why do I-- now.
Miss-- get out.
Oh.
[Music]
F, f, f.
Excuse me, Ms. Ackerman.
What?
I'm Spencer shay,
carly's older brother.
What do you have there?
Frozen yogurt.
There's no eating in my classroom.
Sit down.
Yes, ma'am.
So, principal Franklin said
you wanted to speak to me
about carly's behavior.
That's right.
She sassed me in front
of my entire class.
Right.
We talked about it and
she regrets her sass.
But she felt she needed
to defend Freddie.
She felt like it wasn't fair for--
did I--did I say something?
Hey, come on.
Don't cry.
Blue skies.
No.
Why are you crying?
Well, this is how I use to get carly
to stop crying when she was little.
Oh.
And if that didn't work, little
carly can expect a surprise visit
from the tickle monster.
Oh.
Now, now.
I cannot take-- I can't take this.
Stop.
I'm sorry.
Just that I recently broke up with
my boyfriend and it's been rough.
Oh, don't beat yourself up.
We've all been through
some bad breakups.
Yeah.
So, do you have a girlfriend now
or-- nope, I got a goldfish,
but we're just friends.
So, do you wanna go get
some coffee or something?
Sure.
I make great coffee.
I also have cookies, the soft kind.
Really?
Uh-huh.
Wanna come over?
That sounds nice.
Well then, through the
door, teacher lady.
It's okay, little guy.
[Music]
Oh.
You want me to stop?
No, it hurts too good.
Miss Ackerman?
Oh, hi, carly.
Hi.
Uh, not that I'm not happy to
see you, but why are you here
standing on my brother?
'Cause she has magic feet.
Oh.
I spent six months in Thailand learning
the art of back-walking massage.
Oh, those thailamanians
taught you good.
So, coffee, snacks, back-walking.
What's going on here?
Well, after our guardian-teacher
conference at your school,
we decided to come back here
for coffee and cookies.
Soft cookies.
Okay.
Well, I'm just gonna go
upstairs and try to make myself
comfortable with all this.
No, why don't you hang down
here with us for a while?
You can watch me give
Spencer a haircut.
Try it and I'll call
the scissor police.
Oh, give me that hair.
No.
Give me-- come here,
Spencer-- I love my hair.
I love it.
Come on.
It's all luxurious.
A little bit.
No.
I know you've been very pretty.
Okay, everyone.
I know you were all expecting a test
today, but instead I've decided
to give you all a-pluses
and caramel apples.
Oh, yeah.
Pass those around while
I make a phone call.
Okay.
Spencer dating miss
Ackerman is the best thing
that's happened at this
school since that lunch lady
fell in that giant gravy pot.
Hi, Spencer.
No, I was just missing you.
Yeah.
Did you get my text message?
Did you think it was cute?
No, you are.
Oh my, stop it, I can't take it.
It's just a little weird
seeing a teacher in my house.
Weird, how?
Weird like when she comes
over for dinner, I feel like
I have to raise my hand
to say, "pass the peas."
Eww, peas?
Not the point.
Yeah, the point is this
could not get better.
Hey, kids.
Instead of class tomorrow, how
would you all like to come
ice skating with Spencer and me?
Yeah.
Just got better.
[Music]
[Oven bell ringing]
Ah.
[Doorbell chiming]
Carly, could you get the door?
I'm not dressed yet.
Okay.
Oh, miss Ackerman, you
look sort of like hot.
Really?
Yeah.
Come on in.
Spencer is just finishing
getting dressed.
Oh, hey.
I--I just got the new
cable for the--whoa.
I also said "whoa."
Hi, Freddie.
What are you doing here?
I was just, uh, coming over to
help--work on a Web show with carly.
Whoa.
Okay, why don't we go upstairs
before you start drooling?
Have fun, you guys.
Go.
Wow, you look fantastic.
Thanks.
I got you a present.
What for?
Our one week anniversary.
Ah, how great are you?
Very.
Open it.
No, a pearpod?
Uh-huh, and it's loaded up with
500 of the best songs ever.
Five hundred songs, that
must've cost you a fortune.
No.
No, pearpod wasn't cheap, but
I just downloaded the songs
from one of those
music-sharing websites.
Oh, I think you've got something
boiling over in your stove.
Ah.
Whew, you saved my soup's
life, which means you deserve
some passion fruit punch.
Hmm, sweet.
Uh-huh.
Uhm.
So, where were you today
between 3:15 and 3:40?
What do you mean?
I called you one, two, three, four,
five, six times between 3:15 and 3:40
and you didn't pick up.
You write down every time you call me?
Well, we're dating.
I'd like to know where you are.
Every minute of every day?
Yes.
Really?
Really.
Oh.
I'm gonna go carve Mr.
chicken now.
All right.
So, where do you think you were?
Just take a guess.
I--I don't know.
I think, uh, maybe I was-- liar.
Love me.
Ah.
[Music]
Okay, how about this?
What if you guys do an "iCarly"
segment where you compare vegetables?
What?
You talk about squash and
carly talks about asparagus?
What?
You see, this is why carly and me
are the creative ones, and you're
the technical producer who
really shouldn't talk
so much in these meetings.
Carly.
Let's take a break.
Yeah.
Let's talk about how awesome
it is that Ackerman
never gives us homework anymore.
Yeah, we really owe Spencer.
Big time.
Can you believe how mean Ackerman got
after her last boyfriend dumped her?
Oh, she was gonna ruin our lives.
No doubt.
We're just lucky that-- hey.
Hey.
Where's miss Ackerman?
Oh, she left.
I dumped her.
Hey, Freddie.
[Makes sound]
I can't talk.
I'm trying to prepare for miss
Ackerman's pop quiz on chapter seven.
We're having a pop quiz?
Probably.
You saw how she treated us
last time she got dumped.
Oh man, he is right.
Give me that thing.
I gotta start writing
stuff down on my arms.
How much information can
you write on two arms?
Yeah.
I'm gonna need more space.
I'll be in the bathroom.
Wait, the book.
Get your own book.
That is my own--ah.
Ooh, miss Ackerman's coming.
Be cool.
Maybe she won't notice us.
Good morning, carly.
Good morning, Freddie.
How are two of my
favorite students today?
Uh, fine.
Good.
Uh, you sure are in a good mood.
Yeah, why wouldn't I be?
Well, we sort of heard that you
and Spencer broke up last night.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
We just had a little spat.
No, Spencer and I are
still very much together.
Oh.
So, no pop quiz today?
Of course not, you silly goose people.
Here, take your book.
I'm all set.
You don't need to be.
We just saw miss Ackerman.
No pop quiz.
So I did this for nothing?
[Music]
Hi, we need to talk.
Sure, in a minute.
I gotta finish pumping the guns.
Pump your guns later.
Miss Ackerman's on her way over here.
She thinks you two are still dating.
Oh.
What is wrong with that woman?
She's loony, loony in the head.
Man, why didn't you call and tell me?
I could've been in Canada by now.
Well, I don't think Canada's
gonna-- [doorbell chiming]
[Screaming]
It's her.
Why couldn't I've
been born with wings?
You're not a cockatoo.
Be a man.
All right.
I'm gonna set that lady straight.
No.
Right.
What?
Spencer.
We have to?
Don't upset her?
But I don't wanna go out with her.
I know.
Tell her that, but say it nicely and
sweetly so she doesn't ruin our lives
in school.
Okay, nicely.
And sweetly.
I'll be upstairs.
Boo.
[Screaming]
Hi, Lauren.
What a surprise.
So where should we go
for dinner tonight?
Do you like Italian food?
Yeah, uh, but Lauren-- I know we had
a little argument, but it's okay.
I'm not mad at you anymore, and
I brought you a panda pig.
A panda pig?
Yeah.
You said your two favorite animals
were a panda bear and a pig.
So I cut off the head of a pig
and I sewed it onto the body
of a panda bear.
For you.
Uhh, that's not weird.
Lauren, I don't wanna go
out with you anymore.
Spencer, I think you're
just overreacting.
No.
I think you're under-reacting.
Seriously, I don't wanna date you.
If you're trying to tell
me something, just say it.
I don't want to date you.
Fine.
And I'm just gonna do this.
That was a loud slam.
Did you break up with her?
Yup.
She didn't handle it well.
Were you gentle and sweet?
Yes, but she wasn't.
[Music]
Okay, class.
This pop quiz is going to count for
90 percent of your final grade.
Uh, miss Ackerman, you
forgot to give me a quiz.
That's right, because I
already graded yours.
You give me an f on a
quiz I never took?
That's right.
F, f, f, f-iny, f, f.
Okay, that is jenk.
Life is jenk because sometimes,
certain little girls' brothers
dump you for no good reason.
Miss Ackerman, I didn't mean to--
there's no talking during the quiz.
But it's not my fault.
That tears it.
You give me 100 jumping jacks.
Huh?
That's so not fair.
You too, flapjack.
One hundred jumping jacks
with her in the corner.
Man, you're off your nut.
Is that so?
Well, then, I'm gonna-- yeah, yeah.
I know.
Now, I gotta go do jumping jacks.
No.
You are gonna wash my car.
Faster.
I want those faster.
I wanna see you sweating.
[Music]
What are we gonna do?
We're gonna tell Spencer to call miss
Ackerman and start dating her again.
No, I'm not gonna make my
brother's life miserable
just to make ours easier.
Come on.
Havin' a miserable life
is not all that bad.
Sometimes my mother laughs.
Why can't Spencer just date her?
'Cause the woman's a big
bottle of crazy sauce.
But-- but what?
--I think I might know
a way to fix this.
Good.
How?
"Icarly."
Our Web show?
No, our potato farm.
[Music]
Okay.
Now to close the show--
--we're gonna do something
a little different on "iCarly."
Please say "hello"
to someone you've met here
before, my big brother Spencer.
[Cheering]
Thanks for coming, Spence.
Do you know why you're here?
No, because you wouldn't
tell me why I'm here.
That's 'cause we have a
little surprise for you.
Ooh.
Come on out here, miss Ackerman.
[Cheering]
Yeah.
What is going on?
Just go with it.
Oh.
All right.
This is our history teacher who very
kindly agreed to appear on our show.
Hello.
Spencer and miss Ackerman
have been dating.
But they've been having
some relationship problems.
So we're gonna talk to them.
And then you guys could vote
online right here at iCarly.Com--
--to tell us whether it's time for
them to-- I'm not comfortable
with this.
Shh.
So Spencer, why do you feel
that you and miss Ackerman
are having problems?
Well, she seemed nice at first, but
then I realized she's totally insane--
not my type.
And miss Ackerman, where do
you feel things went wrong?
I don't know.
I tried to be a good girlfriend.
I bought him presents.
What kind of presents?
Well, a customized stuffed animal.
Oh, and a brand new pearpod
with 500 songs on it.
Wow, a lot of songs.
You buy 'em all on peartunes?
No, I just downloaded them from one
of those music-sharing websites,
but it's not about how much a person
spends, it's the thought that counts.
You make a good point.
Okay, "iCarly" viewers.
It's time to vote.
But I can't-- right
here at iCarly.Com.
Just look under the pics of Spencer and
miss Ackerman-- and vote make up--
--or break up.
Can I say one more thing
before they vote?
No.
Sit down.
[Music]
Is that it?
That's it.
Well, what's the vote?
The "iCarly" viewers said that you
and Spencer should-- break up.
[Cheering]
I'm deeply sorry.
Yeah, right.
Listen, we know you feel bad.
Want a bite of my burrito?
No.
And if the vote says that we shouldn't
be together, then I hate you
and the Internet.
Ow.
Okay, what was the point of all this?
Now, she's just gonna be mean and
vicious to you guys at school.
I don't know.
Lot of people watch "iCarly."
And sometimes-- --we make sure
certain specific people watch.
Hmm, yes.
Yes, we do.
You guys are up to something and
I don't wanna know what it is.
[Music]
I hope you all haven't made
any plans for this weekend
'cause you're gonna be up to
your eyeballs in homework.
When?
Soon.
And today, you will all write
1,000 words on why men
are dirty, rotten, stinktacious,
ungrateful-- Lauren Ackerman.
Yes, who are you people?
FBI.
You are under arrest?
Arrest?
For what?
Five hundred counts of illegally
downloading music on the Internet.
Well, you have no proof.
Yes, we do.
Ma'am.
I believe all the proof we
need is on this pearpod.
And you admitted it last night
on those kids' Web show.
Which we recorded.
You set me up.
That's a lie.
No, we set her up.
Oh, yeah.
So now, what do we do?
Yeah, we should probably tell
principal Franklin that our teacher's
been arrested.
Or we could go ice skating.
Yeah.
Hey, "iCarly" people.
You guys know how you do wake
up Spencer on iCarly.com?
Okay, watch me wake up my dad with
a bucketful of ping-pong balls.
Matthew, Katie.
Matthew, come back here right now.
Mmm.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Repair and Synchronization by
Easy Subtitles Synchronizer 1.0.0.0